omictools.com 2019-03-21

# Cookie policy - omicX

The aim of omicX is to help the biomedical community in the identification and use of bioinformatics tools. 

This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website. 

## Editor

The site editor is omicX, a limited liability company with a share capital of € 114,233.30. 

Registered with the Rouen Registry of Commerce and Companies under the number 790 202 006\. 

Head office : 72 rue de la République - 76140 Le Petit-Quevilly, France 

E-Mail: contact@omictools.com 

Publications Director: Arnaud Desfeux 

Tel: +33 2 79 02 75 22 

## Hosting

The hosting provider is OVH, a limited liability company with a share capital of € 10,069,020. 

Registered with the Lille Registry of Commerce and Companies under the number 424 761 419\. 

Head office: 2 rue Kellermann 59100 Roubaix, France 

Publications Director: Octave KLABA 

Tel: +33 72 10 10 07 

## What information we collect about you

We collect information when you voluntarily complete our form to register on our site. 

We only collect information to provide you the service you expect from us. 

We collect information about the way you navigate our website using cookies. 

## How we use the information about you

omicX provides access to its website which mainly consists of a workflow for data analysis for omics, notably genomics, transcriptomics, proteomics and metabolomics. All data analysis tools have been classified by omic technologies, applications and analytical steps. 

omicX collects information about you to: 

  * introduce you to the biomedical omics community using the website; 
  * keep you up to date about new services on the website, if you agree. 

We use the information we collect to personalise your visits to our website in order to improve your experience of finding optimal targeted tools for your bioinformatics analyses. 

omicX will not share your information for marketing or any other purposes with companies outside omicX. 

We will keep your personal data for as long as you are signed-up to use and access our website. 

## Access to your information and correction

We collect information about you according to the French Law n°78-17 dated 6 January 1978 on information technology, data files and civil liberties, as amended or any legislation amending or replacing it (i.e., a Data Protection Act). According to the law, you have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. 

If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the addresses you will find in the “How to contact us” section below. 

We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. 

You can ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. You can, by simple request, exercise all your rights in accordance with the legislation in force. 

## Cookies

Cookies are text files which ask permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree it is used to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. 

For further information visit: 

You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites explain how to remove cookies from your browser. 

However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result. 

## Other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. 

This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you leave our website to connect to other websites you should read their own privacy policies. We cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites. 

## Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. 

This privacy policy was last updated on 26 October 2017. 

## How to contact us

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you: 

  * By email : contact@omictools.com 
  * Or write to us at: omicX, 72 rue de la République, 76140 Le Petit-Quevilly, France
